牛排五分钟后就好
Steaks will be ready in five minutes.
你这是在暴殄天物
You're destroying those things.
-杰 少点意见 -恕难从命
- Ay, Jay, leave him alone. - No, I'm sorry,
那头牛已经吃够了苦头
but that cow has suffered long enough.
-真幽默 -等等
- Fun. - Wait.
别玩了 晚饭马上就好
Hang on. Dinner's ready in five minutes.
教练布置我们练习带球上篮
Coach wants us to practice layups.
超难的动作 是舞蹈与力量的怪混搭
They are deceptively hard- a curious mix of dance and strength.
-你这又把档次拉低了 -抱歉
- You're making it lame again. - Sorry.
-天啊 那个教练 -我讨厌那家伙
- Ay, Dios mio, that coach. - Oh, I hate that guy.
他激发了俩小子的积极性
He seems to have the kids motivated.
爸 你没亲眼见过那家伙
Oh, Dad, you haven't seen him.
他对小家伙们又是讽又是骂
He taunts the kids. He's abusive.
这要是在哥伦比亚足联 老早之前
Listen, if this was a Colombian soccer league, long time ago,
队里孩子就会把他拉出去 咔嚓
one of the kids would have taken that guy out and-
教练本就该严格要求他们
A coach is supposed to ride the kids hard.
-菲尔 你说句话 -那家伙过分了
- Phil, help me out here. - He's a mean man.
-你真是妇人之仁 -你去看场比赛就明白了
-Oh, you're such a woman. - Come to the game. You'll see.
那家伙真的很操蛋
This guy's a real motherscratcher.
原谅我的脏话 歌洛莉亚
Pardon the language, Gloria.
只对歌洛莉亚说吗
"Gloria"?
他最好淡定点
He better cool it,
否则就别怪左将军和右元帅出手了
or I'm gonna introduce him to the Captain and Tennille.
不好意思 迟了 我工作缠身
Sorry we're late. I was at work.
-他最近爱念工作 -烧烤快乐
- Oh, he loves to say that. - And happy barbecue.
自从米奇尔待业家中
Oh. Since Mitchell is between jobs,
我就在一家贺卡店找了份兼职
I've taken a part-time job at a greeting card store,
我爱死这份工作了
which I love.
还有 因为我有员工折扣
Plus, with my discount,
我们可省下了一笔
we're saving a fortune.
花一大笔钱去买贺卡 哪里算省钱了
How is spending a ton of money on greeting cards saving us a fortune?
算算就知道了
It's math.
才不是 我算给你看
It's really not. Look it up.
-六折 -2.95美元
- Forty percent off. - 2.95.
-3.95美元 -六折 六折
-3.95. - Forty percent off. Forty percent off.
米奇尔 我有个高尔夫球友
Mitchell, I got this golf buddy of mine.
人不错 事业有成 你们找机会谈谈
Great guy. Super successful. You two should talk.
没准他有适合你的工作
It could mean a job for you.
谢了 爸 但是我
Oh, thanks, Dad, but I'm-
我现阶段还没找工作的打算
I'm not really looking for anything right now.
-不过 -对 没错
- But- - Yeah, that's right.
有我挣钱养家
With me bringing home the bacon,
米奇尔不急着找工作
Mitchell doesn't have to rush into anything.
我知道你们那个只要贺卡不要钱计划
Yeah, I know you have all that greeting card "Screw you" Money,
但 跟这家伙谈谈
but, uh, talk to the guy?
我跟他说 你明早会给他电话
He's expecting your call in the morning.
-爸 我心领了 但以后 -受不了了
Dad, I appreciate it, but in the future- I can't stand this.
对不起 但是我
I am sorry, but I-
不行 那几块牛排五分钟前就烤好了
No. Those steaks have been done for five minutes.
我得把它们从烤架上夹下来
I'm taking 'em off the grill.
不好意思 你的心情我懂
I'm sorry. I know how it feels
什么事他都要插上一脚
to have him stick his nose where it doesn't belong.
没什么 又不是第一次了
No biggie. It's just Jay being Jay.
总有一天我也会为人岳父
But one day I'm gonna be a grandfather,
到时各位最好都把自个儿的"肉"藏好了
and then everybody better hide their meat.
这美女是谁
Ooh. Who's she?
一点都不好笑
I hate it when you do that.
-这帅哥是谁 -查理·宾格温
- Who's he? - It's Charlie Bingham.
就是我爸让我联系的那个人
He's the guy that my dad wanted me to call.
我搜了他 看
I googled him. Look.
他是"地球人"服装企业的老板
Oh, he owns Earthgear Apparel.
我的滑雪裤就是这牌子的
I have their ski pants.
是吗 你又 你又不滑雪
Really? You don't- You don't ski.
我有好几件工装裤 我也没在码头上班呀
I have cargo pants and I don't work at the docks.
天啊 真是让我自惭形秽
God, I feel like such a slacker.
他年纪轻轻就已大有作为
I mean, he has done so much for being so young.
你看 他创立了不少
Okay, look. He's opened up a dozen
环保基金会和管理委员会
environmental foundations and conservancies.
-真牛 -那你要给他电话了
- Wow. - So, you gonna- you gonna call him?
我没想好 你知道的
I don't know. I mean, you know,
我们之前说好了的
I sort of promised myself and you...
我先休息一段时间 而且
that I'd take a little time off, and-
-而且你也享受这份闲暇 -没错
- And you are loving your time off. - Totally.
我快要抓狂了
I am losing my mind.
虽然我爱莉莉
As much as I love Lily-
把她看得比什么都重
which is, you know, more than life itself-
我 没办法做个居家奶爸
I am- whoo- not cut out to be a stay-at-home dad.
但该轮到卡梅隆了
No, but it's Cameron's turn.
该轮到他到外面
It's Cameron's turn to be out in the world...
跟其他成年人打交道 而我待在家里
interacting with other grown-ups while I get to stay at home...
把《爱探险的朵拉》游戏给解决掉
and-and plot the death of Dora the Explorer.
比如拿砖头塞满她背包
Like to fill her backpack with bricks
再把她扔进拐杖糖河里
and throw her into Candy Cane River.
我不知道 我应该 应该打给他吗
So, I don't know. Should I- Should I call him?
我觉得 打了让你爸死心也好
I don't know. Maybe just to get your dad off your back.
-没错 没错 -我觉得
- Yeah. Yeah. - I mean,
我可不想你现在去上班
because the last thing I want for you is to take a job right now.
我对现状很满意
I am loving our life.
我正陷入绝境
I am in a really dark space.
与莉莉分开简直像酷刑一样
Being away from my Lily is literally torture.
但我又不能给米奇尔压力
And I can't pressure Mitchell,
但我真的真的真的想他快点再就业
but I really, really, really just want him to get a job...
这样我又能做回居家奶爸兼贤妻了
so I can go back to being a stay-at-home dad/trophy wife!
小子 加油
Guys, come on!
加把劲 姑娘们 跑起来
Come on, ladies! Move it!
天啊 乌龟都比你们爬得快
Goodness gracious! Turtles run faster!
跑起来
Come on!
你还能跑得再慢一点吗
Could you run any slower?
我敢说你们跑得更慢都行
I dare you to run slower!
-你看 -他不过是在激发大家斗志
- You see? - He's just trying to light a fire.
待会儿我就把丫给"治"了
Oh, I'll light him on fire!
为什么老是要我来看这玩意儿
Why do I always have to come to these things?
因为你爱你弟弟
Because you love your brother.
那为什么你不让他来我的管弦音乐会
Why don't you make him come to my orchestra concerts?
因为我们爱你弟 好样的卢克
Because we love your brother. Good job, Luke.
投篮
Shoot!
迪尔加多 你是要把我气死吗
Delgado, you're killing me, man!
不管怎样我都爱你 曼尼
I love you, Manny, no matter what!
跑起来
Come on!
好 很好
Okay. That's great.
好的 我再给你回复 对
Okay, well, I'll let you know. Right.
就这样 再见
All right. Bye.
查理·宾格温邀请我们
Uh, so, Charlie Bingham just invited us over...
去他的海边别墅聊聊
to his beach house for a little get-together.
是嘛 你是怎么答复他的
Oh. Uh, what did you say?
我说我先跟你商量下
I said I'd check with you.
你觉得要去吗
I mean, what do you think?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得推掉人家的盛情邀请不大礼貌
Well, I think it'd be rude not to hear him out.
-没错 是这样 -没错
- Yeah. I mean, yeah. You're probably right. - Yeah.
-那就去 -好
- Okay. - Cool.
别过虑了 我不会再就业的
And don't worry. You know, I'm not gonna take any job.
你最好不要
You better not.
我太想
I just miss-
我
I just-
我太想 我的烤奶酪三明治了
I just miss... my grilled cheese sandwiches!
表现不错 卢克
You're doing great, Luke-
如果是比谁打得烂得话
if your goal is to suck!
-菲尔 你 -我出手
- Phil, you- - I'm on it.
-好 -等等我
- Okay. - Wait for me.
-教练 -什么
- Hey, Coach. - Yeah?
你指导很投入很激情
Uh, look. We appreciate your passion,
但是我们担心
but some of us are worried that
嚷嚷可能会起反效果
the yelling is getting counterproductive.
我心里有数 跑 笨蛋
I got this. Come on, stupid!
不 你没 你有的只是烂态度
No, you don't "Got this." What you got is a bad attitude.
你哪位
Who are you?
我是家长 就是那个
I happen to be the stepfather of-
我是谁不重要 你要做的是
Doesn't matter who. What you need to start doing...
多一些指导 少一些嚷嚷
is a little more coaching and a little less yelling.
因为我要是再听见你叫他们笨蛋
'Cause if I hear you call one of these kids stupid again,
我发誓 我会脱鞋对着你的脑袋砸
I swear to God, I'll throw a shoe at your head.
操 我才懒得教
Screw it. I don't need this.
你觉得你能教得比我好
You think you can do a better job?
你来教啊
You coach.
杰 我刚在跟他谈呢
Jay, you know, I was handling it.
对 我注意到你的小左和小右爆发了
Yeah, I saw how you broke out Peaches and Herb.
是左将军和
It's the Captain and-
听着 你们之前的教练要离开一段时间
Okay. So, your old coach had to leave for a little while.
为什么 他病了吗
Why? Is he sick?
-对 他病得很严重 -那他会死吗
- Yes. He's very, very sick. - Is he going to die?
人皆有一死 孩子们 现在关注当下
Everybody dies, boys. Let's focus on what's important.
一小时后下场就开始了
Our next game is in one hour.
我们要团结一致 重拳出击
We are going to go from being five fingers to being a fist.
-怎么样 -好
- How does that sound? - Great.
-听不到 -好
- I can't hear you. - Great!
就是这样
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout!
各位 我刚和裁判谈过了 我来执教
All right, gentlemen. I talked to the referee. I'm coaching.
-但是我 -菲尔 我以前教过橄榄球
- Oh, really? 'Cause I- - Phil, I coached football.
杰 我之前教过篮球
Jay, I actually coached basketball.
我觉得我能让小家伙们
I think I can get these guys-
别急 让你当助理
Relax. You've already got the assistant job.
现在去给我们带几瓶水好吗
Now you think you can round us up some waters?
-好 -去吧
- Yeah. - Go ahead.
伙计们 你们要这样
Gentlemen, this is what I need.
我要你们把他们打败 打得落花流水
I want you to hit 'em, and I want you to hit 'em hard.
跟岳父相处真不易
Father-in-laws are tough,
因为既不能让他对你呼来喝去
because you can't let 'em push you around...
同时又要对他表示尊重
and you also have to show them respect.
就像是在走钢丝
It's like walking a tightrope.
顺便提一下 我能走 因为我练过
Which, by the way, I can do, because I went to trapeze school.
杰呢 我深表怀疑
Did Jay? I doubt it.
好的 当你进入
All right, when you back into-
亲爱的 我要走了
Honey, I'm gonna take off.
-我去给艾丽克斯买几件衣服 -好的
- I'm gonna buy Alex some clothes. - Okeydoke.
怎么不是你在指导
How come you're not coaching?
因为你爸教过橄榄球
'Cause your dad coached football.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我今晚会补偿你的
And I am going to make it up to you tonight.
-而我会在脑子里想着你爸 -嗯
- And I'll be thinking of your dad while you do. - Mmm.
没心思了
Disturbing.
-菲尔 -来了
- Hey, Phil. - Hey.
怎么样
How's it going?
好着呢 你爸教过橄榄球
Ay. Great. Your dad coached football.
又一个受害同胞
Ah. A fellow victim.
谢谢你帮我们带莉莉 我知道有点急
Thank you again for taking care of Lily. I know it's last-minute.
别见外了
Ay. Don't be silly.
我们或许该待一会儿
We'll probably just stick around for a few minutes.
她不跟我们在一起的时候会抓狂 所以
You know how fussy she gets when we pass her off, so-
-她好着呢 -对
- Oh. She seems fine. - Yeah.
你现在要上班
Ay. I think she's getting used to
我看她已经习惯你不在身边了
being away from you now that you have the new job.
妈妈以你为豪
Mwah! So proud of you.
-我们得谈谈 -好 怎么了
- We need to talk. - Okay. What happened?
妈 我爱你
Mom, I love you,
但你的鼓励
but your words of encouragement
鼓励了其他队员开我玩笑
encourage the other kids to make fun of me.
懂了
Ay. Okay.
下场比赛我会一声不发 保证
I won't say anything else on the next game. Promise.
你我都很清楚 你的拉丁热血会让你的保证无效
We both know that your Latin blood makes that impossible.
我觉得你下场回避一下会更好
I think it would be better if you didn't come to the next game.
我就知道
I know.
-我们家简直就像贫民窟 -就是
- I hate our house. - I know.
这是 这是干嘛用的
What's- What's this thing?
不知道 但是很高级
I don't know, but it's fancy.
别 别在上面跳 来
Stop- Stop playing with it. Come on.
别 别弄坏了
Just- Don't break it.
-米奇尔 -是的
- Hey, Mitchell! - Yes.
-查理·宾格温 -幸会
- Charlie Bingham. - Nice to meet you.
-你好 -这是我的伴侣卡梅隆·塔克
- Hi. - This is my partner, Cameron Tucker.
-幸会 -卡梅隆
- Pleasure. - Cameron.
我们刚刚直开进来
So, we just went ahead and
停在车道那个圆盘上面
parked on that round thingy in the driveway.
-这样 没问题吧 -没问题
- Is that- That's fine, right? - No problem.
那是转盘 这样你就不用倒车了
It's a turntable, so you don't have to back out.
你有车用转盘 穿着胶皮衣
You have a car turntable and you're wearing rubber.
就像是高富帅蝙蝠侠
You're like Batman.
我还真是
I really am.
进来吧
Come on in.
把音乐关小点
Turn the music down!
寒舍 见谅
Pardon the get-up.
今天的浪很棒 你们冲浪吗
Killer waves today. You guys surf?
只网上冲浪 跟卖家讨价还价
Um, only for bargains on the Web.
大伙打个招呼
Everybody say hi.
-你们好 -你们好
- Hi. - Hello.
-你们好 -这是茱莉
-Hi. - That's Jolie.
她打牌出老千 你就有
She cheats at poker. You do.
那边是我的女友珍妮
And that's my girlfriend, Jenny.
她调的玛格丽塔好极了 来一杯
She makes a hell of a margarita. Want one?
-当然要 -不 现在 好
- Absolutely. - Oh, not right- Okay.
各位 米奇尔·普里契特和他的伴儿卡梅隆
Everybody, Mitchell Pritchett and his partner, Cameron.
生意伙"伴" 做并购的
Business partners. Mergers and acquisitions.
-开玩笑啦 我们是同志 -别多话
- I'm kidding. We're gay. - Stop talking.
没压力的时候 我是社交场上的好手
When things are relaxed, I'm great in social situations.
阿尔冈琴圆桌会我也能轻松应对
I would have fit in at the Algonquin Round Table.
但是压力大的时候 我就紧张
But when the stakes are high, I get a little tense.
我估计会直接把那圆桌打翻
I'd be the guy that would knock over the round table.
然后桃乐茜·帕克[已故名诗人]会嘲弄我
Then Dorothy Parker would make a quip,
詹姆斯·托伯[已故名作家]大笑
James Thurber would laugh,
最后我哭着鼻子 掩面而逃
and then I would end up leaving, crying.
-你已经潜逃多久了 -什么
- How long you been on the lam? - What?
宝贝 你四周顾视像是有联邦探员在追捕你
Honey, you are looking around like the feds are after you.
才没有 我们赶快把衣服买完
No, I'm not. Let's just get this over with.
好吧
Oh. All right.
不好 是她们
Oh, no. It's them.
她们不是你的同学嘛
Oh! Oh, you know those girls from school.
-嘿 -走 这边
- Hey! - Let's go! Over here.
-你 你这是怎么了 -没什么
- What- What is your problem? - Nothing.
一小时后车上见
I'll meet you at the car in an hour.
求你了 妈 求你了
Please, Mom. Please.
-嗨 珍娜 -好
- Hi, Jenna. - Hi.
就这样 我的宝贝女儿长成了少女
And just like that- my baby girl became a teenager.
她进入了那个讨厌的阶段
She entered that dreaded phase
我的存在让她感到尴尬
where my very existence embarrasses her.
我 我来安慰一下
I-I think I can help.
你跟你妈不一样
You're not your mom.
哇 这是你妈的经典表情
Wow. That's your mom.
背脊一阵发凉
Oh, I just got chills.
先要坦白我是你的粉丝
So, first off, I'm a fan.
-在法庭上有一面之缘 -当真
- Saw you in court once. - Seriously?
是的 梅休诉普罗泰克一案
Yeah. Mayhew versus Propyltech.
-你是个不可多得的好律师 -不敢当
- You are a good lawyer. - I don't know.
如果我的离婚交给你处理
If you'd handled my divorce,
这房子肯定是现在的两倍大
this house would be twice as big.
他好到不行 你可争不赢他
Oh, he's better than good. Try winning an argument with him.
-昨晚我想去吃印度菜 -你又来了
- Last night I wanted to have Indian food- - And we're talking again.
康奈尔大学和哥伦比亚法学院第一名
Top of your class at Cornell and Columbia Law.
工作机会一大把
Had your pick of jobs,
却选择专攻环保法 直到上个月
but instead chose to work in environmental law- until last month.
他还曾是优秀的花样滑冰运动员
Well- And he used to be a really great figure skater.
-为什么不干了 -他姐不想滑了
- Why'd you quit? - His sister lost interest,
-然后就 -他问我为什么辞职
- and then there was- - He means my job.
跟我说说花样滑冰也行
Could tell me about figure skating too.
这个 她确实不想滑了
Um, well, it was- She did lose interest.
-行了 -好
- That's enough. - Okay.
小美人啊小美人
Ay, que linda. Ay, que linda.
天啊 我不知道你们也来这边
Oh, my gosh. I didn't know you guys were gonna be here.
嘿 克莱尔
Hola, Claire.
嗨 莉莉
Hi, Lily.
今天真是看够篮球赛了
I had enough basketball for one day.
可不是嘛 来 抱抱 小可爱
Oh, I know. Come here, sweetie.
小可爱 你爱我 你要我给你买裙子
Oh, sweet thing. You love me and you want me to buy you a dress.
是 但是我先要给她买几双鞋子
Ay. But I'm gonna buy her some shoes first. Mmm.
什么 莉莉 要我给你买裙子吗
What's that, Lily? Do you want me to buy you a dress?
她说"好"
She said "Yes."
"好"
"Yes"?
她没说"好"
She did not say "Yes."
好 数到三说"胜"
Okay, "Win" On three.
一二三 胜
One, two, three- Win!
别忘了掩护走位
Don't forget the pick and roll.
-对手不知道怎么防 -菲尔
- These guys won't know how to defend it. - Phil,
-别把我的队员搞糊涂了好吗 -好
- try not to confuse my boys, okay? - Okay.
-我睡了你女儿 -什么
- I sleep with your daughter. - What?
好运
Good luck!
好 上场 快快快 跑起来
All right. Let's go! Let's go! Come on. Let's go!
动起来 快快快 记住我说的
Let's get out there. Hustle up. Get the tip, get the tip.
注意 抢球 走
Watch, skip and go.
没事 跑起来 跑起来
Oh! All right. Keep the hustle, keep the hustle.
加油 小子 别让他们掌握主动
Come on, boys. Don't let 'em push you around.
没事 防守好
Oh! All right, little defense!
注意防守
Play defense!
我稍微侦探了一下
I did a little scouting,
对手只有两个投手
and the other team only has two shooters.
如果我们把他俩防好
If we isolate both of them-
好 菲尔 好 谢谢 好
Good, Phil, good. Thank you. Good.
曼尼 集中精神 你看什么呢
Manny, pay attention! What are you looking at?
什么
What?
那是2004年的事情了
And that was in 2004.
跟我说说
So, tell me this.
太阳能电厂会有哪方面的阻力
What are the regulatory challenges of a solar farm?
各方面都有 农业方面
Uh, well, you know, it could be anything- uh, agricultural-
军队方面 物种保护
Military, protected species,
讽刺的是 甚至会牵扯某些环保组织
ironically, even some, uh, environmental groups.
你该喝完了吧
I think you got all of it.
应该没了
Think you got it.
对 我去满上
Yeah. I'm just gonna freshen this up.
-问你个问题 -什么
- Let me ask you a question. - Yeah.
留胡子感觉如何
How do you like the beard?
我想留 珍妮不同意
I'm thinking of growing one. Jenny's against it.
这个 我觉得挺好
Oh. Well, I-I've been very happy with mine.
好 决定留了
That's it. I'm doin' it.
我挣不少钱 我想用来做些好事
Look, I've made a fortune. I want to use it for some good.
我需要律师帮我定位
I need a lawyer to help me navigate.
我挺喜欢你 你懂我 你意下如何
I like you. You get me. So, in or out?
我真是
I just-
-对不起 -没什么
- I'm very sorry. - It's okay.
这是一个重大的决定
Um, that's a very big question.
当然 我要先跟我家那位
You know, I'm obviously gonna have to
莽撞的"野牛" 商量一下
go talk to my- bull in a china shop.
-失陪一下 -行
- I'll be right back. - Sure.
好好谈 这可是人生重大决定
Talk it over. It's a major life decision.
嘿 珍妮 胡子我留定了
Hey, Jenny! The beard is on!
莉莉 该给你买美美的鞋子了
Okay, Lily, it's time to buy you beautiful shoes.
不不不 我刚看到有条很好看的裙子
Oh, no, no, no. I saw another really cute dress for her.
但是她已经买了6件新裙子了
Ay. But she has already six new dresses.
她现在要的是绑带鞋
What she needs is strappy shoes.
艾丽克斯过来了 待会见
There's Alex. I'll-I'll see you later.
艾丽克斯 亲爱的
Alex, honey. Hi.
妈 我说了待会儿车上见
Mom, I said I'd meet you at the car.
拿去
Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
还想要个女儿吗
Still wish you had a daughter?
-曼尼不想我去看他比赛 -深表同情
- Manny didn't want me at the game today. - Oh, I'm sorry.
-没什么 -不 怎么会没什么 烂透了
- It's okay. - No, it's not okay. It sucks.
我想念宝宝 他们从不会让我们走开
I miss babies. They never tell you to go away.
对 也不会让我们在车里等
Yeah. Or wait in the car.
我不知道你怎么想
I don't know about you,
但我不会站在这自怨自艾
but I'm not gonna stand here and feel sorry for myself.
你知道我们该做什么吗
You know what we should do?
把肚子搞大
Get pregnant.
我想说的是去吃冰淇林
I was gonna say go for ice cream.
好的 我们先实施你的方案
Okay. We'll do yours first. Great.
卢克 卢克
Luke! Luke!
周围没有对手 有什么好防守的
It's hard to guard a player if there's no player near you!
这边情况如何
We good in the hood?
那帮家伙简直让人倍受打击
This is a uniquely frustrating group of boys.
确实 我有个小建议 停止联防
I hear you. Um, one thing that might help- instead of a zone,
转而进行一对一防守
if you switch to a simple man-to-man.
-我可以的 -是吗
- I got this. - Really?
但是根据记分板数据
'Cause according to the scoreboard,
你只拿了四分
the only thing you got is four points.
好运
Good luck.
-我要跟你谈谈 -我要跟你谈
- I need to talk to you. - I need to talk to you.
衣服不错
Nice top.
到这来 你 你
Come here. You- You-
小卡 小卡 你得放轻松
Cam- Cam, you have got to relax.
我说过我不会接受新工作的 除非
I told you I wouldn't take a job without-
-快接受吧 -什么
- Take the job. - What?
我要你答应下这份工作
I want you to take the job.
我以为你想让我在家带莉莉呢 我
I thought you liked having me home with Lily. I-
我不想 我是说 我想 我只是
I don't. I mean, I do. I just-
我怀念和莉莉一起的好时光
I miss my time with Lily,
我知道这太自私了 但是
and I know it's selfish of me, but-
-不 我想要工作 -真的吗
- No, I want the job. - You do?
当然 我
Oh, my God, yes.
我爱莉莉 但是我讨厌说话依依呀呀地
I- I love Lily, but I hate baby talk.
我喜欢依依呀呀地说话
I love baby talk.
-答应下这份工作 -答应下来
- Let's go get this job. - Let's get this job.
-好的 -不会吧
- Okay. - Oh, no.
锁住了
It's locked.
那就
Well, just
喂 有人吗
Hello? Hey, guys?
老天啊
Oh, my gosh.
他们听不到 我们困在这了
They're not gonna hear us. We're trapped out here.
别这么一惊一乍的
Just stop being so dramatic.
我们从车库出去 这样
We'll just go through the garage, with the-
难怪他要雇你 你能应对危机
That's why he wants to hire you. You're good in crisis.
天啊 这
Ooh, yeesh. What-
-没开 -再按按看
- It's not opening. - Push it again.
-我听到动静了 但是 -用力点按
- I'm hearing things, but it's not- - Push it harder.
不是这个 这个吗
That's not- Is it this one?
我也听到了 什么声响
I hear something. What is that?
不是 别乱按 住手
No. Stop touching- Stop-
这个 是这个 行了
This- Oh, that was it. All right.
-米奇尔 天啊 这 -天啊
- Mitchell! Oh, my God. Did- - No!
-天啊 -不 小卡
- Oh, my God! - No, Cam!
小卡 我们 我们弄的
Cam, we- Did we do that?
这怎么交代
What are we gonna say?
工作我答应下了
I will take the job.
-不然你哪来钱修车 -对
- Kinda think you have to now. - Yeah.
小伙子 你们一个队的
Guys, you're on the same team!
暂停
Time out!
-暂停 -给我过来
- Time out! - Get over here!
各位 我们刚刚合计的几个战术
Guys, earlier we practiced a few set plays.
哪里提到让你们从队友手中抢球了
Did any of them involve wrestling the ball from your own teammate?
-你说要使出浑身解数的 -没错
- But you said to be aggressive. - Yeah!
但不是对你队友使 待着别动
Not on your own team! Wait here.
得你来教 我干不了
You gotta coach. I can't take it.
-你是在跟我说吗 -是 是跟你说
- You talkin' to me? - Yeah, I'm talkin' to you.
你得接手 我就快输了
You gotta take over. I'm about to lose it out there.
那可真不容易 教练
That sounds tough, Coach.
-你这是怎么回事 -教练 该继续了
- What's your problem? - Hey, Coach! Ticktock.
我之前跟教练交涉 你把我挤开
I was dealing with the coach. You pushed me aside.
我给孩子们指导 你把我挤开
I was dealing with the boys. You pushed me aside.
信不信由你 杰
Believe it or not, Jay,
有些事我比你擅长
there are some things that I am better at than you are.
-砰 终于把话摊开了 -老天啊
- Bam! It's out there. - Oh, for God's sake.
-教练 -他叫你呢
- Coach! - He's calling you.
听着 我能理解你很不爽 好吧
Listen. I don't blame you for being angry. All right?
我习惯了主事 仅此而已
I'm used to taking charge. That's all.
我一开始就该让你来做教练
I should have let you coach from the get-go.
还有呢
And?
-我爱你 -不 烧烤那事儿
- I love you. - No. The barbecue.
噢 老天啊
Oh, for God's sake.
你烤的牛排肯定好吃 不会咬不动
I'm sure your steaks would have been delicious... and not chewy.
-好 我来 -谢谢
- Okay. I'll do it. - Thanks.
所以说青出于蓝而胜于蓝
And so the student becomes the master.
-昔日王者 -算了 不劳你驾
- The once mighty- - You know what? Forget it.
不不不不 我来 我来
No, no, no, no. I'm good. I'm good.
队员们 想不想以赢家的身份走出去
Hey, hey. Guys. Who wants to go out like a champ?
-想 -我
- Yeah! - Me!
就这态度 好 乔迪 你发球给卢克
I love it! Okay, Jordy, you inbound to Luke.
曼尼 你把卢克的防守挡开
Manny, you set a pick on Luke's man
然后去球篮下面候位
and roll to the bucket.
-卢克你知道该怎么做了 -我不知道
- Luke, you know what to do. - No, I don't.
-传地板球给曼尼 -但是 爸
- Bounce-pass to Manny. - But, Dad-
教练 曼尼整个赛季都没进过球
Coach, Manny hasn't taken a single shot all season.
机会来时他会把握住的
Then chances are he'll be open.
好的 队员们 上场了
Okay, guys. Let's bring it out.
嘿 都伸出手来
Hey, hey. Bring it in.
给对手秀秀我们的气势
Let's show these guys what kind of team they're about to beat.
数到三喊"小德伯必胜"
Huh? "Li'I Dribblers" On three.
一二三 小德伯必胜
One, two, three- Li'I Dribblers!
红队场边发球 开始
Okay, red ball. Side out. Here we go.
我的执教理念是什么
What's my coaching philosophy?
-给孩子一只鸟 -就是这样
- Give a kid a bird- - Yes!
他就会像那些怪叔叔一样
And he becomes one of those weird dudes
把鸟放在肩膀四处晃荡
who walks around with a bird on his shoulder.
但给他一双翅膀
But give him a pair of wings,
他就能飞
he can fly.
除非他眼高手低 技术太烂
Unless he has absolutely no hand-eye coordination.
没事 我相信你
Okay, I support you.
妈
Mom.
你晚了20分钟
That was 20 minutes.
妈 我非常非常抱歉
Mom, I am so, so sorry.
我知道我不该这样
I know it's no excuse,
只是我人在学校身不由己
but I've been feeling a lot of pressure at school.
来自朋友圈的压力
You know, with friends.
我非常非常爱你
And I love you so much,
你为我所做的一切我都心存感恩
and I appreciate everything you do for me.
我还是你的乖乖女
I'm still your little girl.
亲爱的 妈妈听你这么说真开心
Oh, honey! That was so sweet.
能给我20美元吗 我们想去看电影
Can I get $20? A bunch of us are going to a movie,
然后再去吃个饭什么的
and we're gonna get something to eat afterwards.
珍娜她哥会载我们回家的
Jenna's brother's gonna take us home.
好 没问题 亲爱的 给你40
Okay. Of course. Sweetie, you know what? Take 40.
-天啊 -没什么 给
- Oh, my gosh. - Yeah. That's right.
-谢谢妈 -去吧 玩得开心
- Thanks, Mom. - Go on. Have a great time.
艾丽克斯 亲爱的 逛街的时候
Oh, Alex, honey? When you're out shopping,
最好给自己买件胸罩
you might wanna pick yourself up a training bra.
我知道你现在用不上
I know you don't need one now,
但你的小咪咪早晚会长出来的嘛
but your little boobies are gonna come in soon.
妈妈爱你 小猫猫
Mommy loves you, kitten!
亲亲 亲亲
Mwah! Mwah!
看你还敢耍我
Teach her to screw with me.
我阻断了防守 然后跑到球篮下
I set a pick and then rolled towards the basket.
卢克把球传给我 我投篮 几乎进了
Luke passed to me. I shot the ball and almost made it.
我今天给莉莉买了件非常萌的裙子
I bought Lily the cutest little dress today.
然后我从对手那里抢到球
And then I stole the ball from the other team,
然后360逆天翻转上篮 几乎灌篮
did a 360 and almost dunked it.
真牛
That's nice.
我今天跟莉莉玩得太开心了
Ay. I just had the best day today with Lily.
那小姑娘萌翻了
That girl's so sweet.
我下周六有比赛 你来看吧
I have a game next Saturday. You could come.
不了 谢谢 我不想去给你丢脸
No, it's okay. I wouldn't want to embarrass you.
那天我应该会带莉莉去吃纸杯蛋糕
I'll probably take Lily out for cupcakes. Mm-hmm.
哦
Okay.
提点一下
Any suggestions?
我一般用耳环哄她开心
I usually go with earrings.